ROP Tour 2026
This is the terrain of the Republic of Panorama
It is a mix of terrain generations from b1.0, b1.8.1, and all the release versions that came after.
In ROP, we have two main Train-based Transport Providers.
This is the IntraWorld Railway, the first railway system in ROP, originally built by NormalFery.
It was then renovated and modernised by TheClashFruit and Myadeleines, using Creative Mode, which became a controversial decision.
What you're seeing now is Northern's H1 Metro. It was built to connect ROP and Chunkia.
It has many stops in important parts of Panorama.
We are now going to visit ROP's Underground Tunnels. They connect many iconic places!
ROP Citizens built these when the surface got too crowded. It connects convenient paths & businesses.
The Gay Bar, The Northern Complex, H1, The Info Centre, and Metro Neue all connect here.
Let's now visit the area on the west side of The Info Centre.
This is the NCB BlurBank vein. NCB used to be an independent bank operated by TCF, but it was eventually merged with BlurBank.
ROP Citizens have a weird obsession with The Letter T and its upside down version.
This is The Northern Complex. A residential and commercial building, ran by The Northern Company.
Here, we can see BlurBank. The biggest bank in the world.
Banking services are no longer that popular, though.
This is The Info Centre. For years, it was the 'official' information source.
Unfortunately, it became unmaintained and ended up not being used anymore.